drivershq.com 2005-03-16

# Drivers Headquarters - Software Drivers and Hardware Drivers

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is the reason we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy informs you how your personal information is processed and utilized. We promise to take the necessary steps to only use your personal information in ways that are compatible with this Policy. 

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from PC Drivers Headquarters, Inc., our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our Web Site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the PC Drivers Headquarters, Inc., its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors. 

If you are purchasing a product from PC Drivers Headquarters, Inc., we will need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order, and to notify you of your order status. We may also use this information to notify you of our related products and services. Credit card and e-mail information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your expressed permission. 

PC Drivers Headquarters, Inc. will disclose personal information and IP addresses, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary. 

Run Free Driver Detective Scan.....

**COMMON SENSE POLICY**  
All driver(s) and names used on this web site are copyrighted and the property of the company supplying the drivers. When using a company's driver you will bound to that company's own legal agreement (we suggest you read the agreements). 

Drivers HeadQuarters is NOT responsible for any damage that the information on this web site may cause to your system. Anything you might attempt, whether inspired by this web site or not, is entirely at your own risk! 

All product names and company names used herein are for identification purposes only and may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. Drivers HeadQuarters is in no way affiliated or representing any of the companies represented on this web site. 

Run Free Driver Detective Scan.....

**REFUND POLICY**  
If we are unable to provide the updated driver that we have presented when you did the free scan for functioning hardware devices we will be happy to provide you with a refund. Please use this contact form and include the information about the driver that was not available for update. 

To request a refund please include your name, date of purchase as this will help expedite your request. All refunds will be processed within 5 business days of receiving the request. If you have additional questions please feel free to contact us. Refunds will not be issued 30 days after date of purchase. 

Thank You, Drivers HeadQuarters.
